

# PROFESSIONAL

SKILLS

PHP
Javascript
Laravel
HTML
CSS
Web Design
Wordpress
SEO
Social Media Strategy
Growth-Driven Design Framework

#### PERSONAL SKILLS

Creative spirit
Reliable and professional
Organized
Time management
Team player
Fast learner
Motivated

### CONTACT

P: +63 905-208-5185 E: decwenceslao@gmail.com dec@brightframework.com

## SOCIAL

linkedin.com/in/xxivth/ https://github.com/xxivth facebook: fb.me/xxivth twitter: @iamxxivth

# DEC RACHELLE WENCESLAO

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

#### **ABOUT**

I am an enthusiastic, creative web developer and designer with 3 years of accumulated experience in the field of web development and design industry. I want to be a part of your team where I can continuously grow professionally and as well contribute to the company's growth and success.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

LEAD WEB DEVELOPER | CREATIVE DESIGN STARTUP Bright Framework | March 2016 - Present

- Developed websites for companies that need help in growing their business online.
- Utilized Growth-Driven Design framework in the web design process to maximize continuous improvement with their website.

TRAINING ASSISTANT | FREELANCE / PROJECT-BASED Mindbroker Corporation | May 2018 - Present

- Assists consultants in facilitating training and workshops for participants coming from the field of customer service, human resource, organizational development, professional image enhancement, and public speaking.
- Helps in designing tailor-fitted programs that are to be conducted.

MANAGER AND SOCIAL MEDIA MARKETER | STARTUP JuanRice Enterprise | Oct 2015 - Apr 2016

- Developed a social media strategy to increase the following of the company website
- Accept orders online thru www.juanrice.ph website and JuanRice.ph Facebook page.

TECHNICAL SUPPORT REPRESENTATIVE | CORPORATE Concentrix, Convergys, Executive Boutique | 2010 - 2015

- Provide client support and technical issue resolution via e-mail, phone and other electronic medium.
- Identify and correct or advise, on operational issues in client computer systems.
- Offer alternative solutions where appropriate with the objective of retaining customers' and clients' business.



# DEC RACHELLE WENCESLAO

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

# PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

PHP
Javascript
Laravel
HTML
CSS
Web Design
Wordpress
SEO
Social Media Strategy
Growth-Driven Design Framework

### PERSONAL SKILLS

Creative spirit
Reliable and professional
Organized
Time management
Team player
Fast learner
Motivated

# CONTACT

P: +63 905-208-5185 E: decwenceslao@gmail.com dec@brightframework.com

## SOCIAL

linkedin.com/in/xxivth/ https://github.com/xxivth facebook: fb.me/xxivth twitter: @iamxxivth

### **EDUCATION**

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT

Tuitt IT Coding Bootcamp | 2018

Recently completed a 3-month intensive coding bootcamp as a Full Stack Web Developer. Designed 3 capstone projects using SQL, HTML, CSS, PHP, Bootstrap, Javascript, Jquery and Laravel.

BACHELOR OF THEOLOGY

Halls of Life Bible college | 2009 Honor Roll 1st year

### **VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE**

TEAM LEAD

Children and Youth Communicators' Team of the Sixth Countrywide Programme for Children (CPC VI) | 2006-2007

I strongly advocate in raising awareness of every child's basic rights and how it should be protected. Our team went to different schools and communities in Davao City in educating both the young ones and the leaders on how to advance the cause.